{
  "recipes": [
    {
      "id": "001",
      "title": "One-Pot Smoky Coriander Chicken & Rice with Esquites",
      "ingredients": ["chicken", "red pepper", "rice"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "558kcal",
        "protein": "46g",
        "carbs": "68g",
        "fat": "11g"
      },
      "tags": ["One-Pot", "Chicken", "Rice"],
      "image_front": "images/one_pot_smokey_chicken_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/one_pot_smokey_chicken_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "002",
      "title": "Creamy Chicken & Pesto Penne With Basil",
      "ingredients": ["chicken", "pesto", "pasta"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "733kcal",
        "protein": "48g",
        "carbs": "74g",
        "fat": "27g"
      },
      "tags": ["Pesto", "Chicken", "Pasta"],
      "image_front": "images/chicken_pesto_pasta_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/chicken_pesto_pasta_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "003",
      "title": "Beef Meatballs with Creamy Linguine",
      "ingredients": ["beef", "pasta"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "830kcal",
        "protein": "48g",
        "carbs": "74g",
        "fat": "37g"
      },
      "tags": ["Beef", "Pasta"],
      "image_front": "images/meatball_tagliatelle_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/meatball_tagliatelle_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "004",
      "title": "Sausage Curry, Coriander Rice & Naan",
      "ingredients": ["sausage", "curry", "rice"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "745kcal",
        "protein": "28g",
        "carbs": "93g",
        "fat": "29g"
      },
      "tags": ["Sausage", "Curry", "Rice"],
      "image_front": "images/sausage_curry_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/sausage_curry_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "005",
      "title": "Indonesian Style Chicken Rendang",
      "ingredients": ["chicken", "curry", "rendang", "rice"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "589kcal",
        "protein": "36g",
        "carbs": "61g",
        "fat": "20g"
      },
      "tags": ["Chicken", "Curry", "Rice"],
      "image_front": "images/rendang_curry_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/rendang_curry_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "006",
      "title": "Brazilian Haddock Moqueca & Zesty Lime Rice",
      "ingredients": ["fish", "curry", "rice"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "546kcal",
        "protein": "28g",
        "carbs": "61g",
        "fat": "20g"
      },
      "tags": ["Fish", "Curry", "Rice"],
      "image_front": "images/fish_moqueca_curry_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/fish_moqueca_curry_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "007",
      "title": "Beef Spaghetti Bolognese",
      "ingredients": ["beef", "pasta"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "834kcal",
        "protein": "46g",
        "carbs": "90g",
        "fat": "31g"
      },
      "tags": ["Beef", "Pasta"],
      "image_front": "images/spag_bol_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/spag_bol_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "008",
      "title": "One-Pot Cheesy Chorizo Risotto",
      "ingredients": ["rice", "risotto", "chorizo"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "599kcal",
        "protein": "23g",
        "carbs": "71g",
        "fat": "24g"
      },
      "tags": ["Rice", "Risotto", "Chorizo"],
      "image_front": "images/cheese_chorizo_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/cheese_chorizo_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "009",
      "title": "Lamb Keema With Spinach",
      "ingredients": ["lamb", "spinach", "rice"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "615kcal",
        "protein": "35g",
        "carbs": "51g",
        "fat": "29g"
      },
      "tags": ["Lamb", "Spinach", "Rice", "Quick", "Fast"],
      "image_front": "images/lamb_keema_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/lamb_keema_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "010",
      "title": "Indonesian Inspired Pork Noodles",
      "ingredients": ["pork", "noodles"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "712kcal",
        "protein": "34g",
        "carbs": "78g",
        "fat": "29g"
      },
      "tags": ["Pork", "Noodles", "Quick", "Fast"],
      "image_front": "images/indo_pork_noodles_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/indo_pork_noodles_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "011",
      "title": "Spicy Cajun Beef & Pork Pepper Rigatoni",
      "ingredients": ["pork", "pasta", "beef"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "854kcal",
        "protein": "42g",
        "carbs": "80g",
        "fat": "39g"
      },
      "tags": ["Pork", "Pasta", "Beef", "Quick", "Fast"],
      "image_front": "images/speedy_cajun_beef_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/speedy_cajun_beef_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "012",
      "title": "Chipotle Black Bean Enchiladas",
      "ingredients": ["beans", "pepper"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "854kcal",
        "protein": "42g",
        "carbs": "80g",
        "fat": "39g"
      },
      "tags": ["Beans", "Mexican", "Enchiladas"],
      "image_front": "images/bean_enchiladas_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/bean_enchiladas_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "013",
      "title": "Bacon & Mushroom Linguine",
      "ingredients": ["bacon", "mushroom", "pasta"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "708kcal",
        "protein": "24g",
        "carbs": "74g",
        "fat": "34g"
      },
      "tags": ["Bacon", "Mushroom", "Pasta", "Quick", "Fast"],
      "image_front": "images/bacon_mushroom_pasta_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/bacon_mushroom_pasta_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "014",
      "title": "Teriyaki Sesame Chicken",
      "ingredients": ["rice", "chicken"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "574kcal",
        "protein": "40g",
        "carbs": "90g",
        "fat": "5g"
      },
      "tags": ["Rice", "Chicken", "Quick", "Fast"],
      "image_front": "images/chicken_teriyaki_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/chicken_teriyaki_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "015",
      "title": "Peri Peri Chicken Breast Traybake",
      "ingredients": ["chicken", "potato"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "659kcal",
        "protein": "37g",
        "carbs": "59g",
        "fat": "25g"
      },
      "tags": ["Chicken", "Potato"],
      "image_front": "images/peri_peri_chicken_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/peri_peri_chicken_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "016",
      "title": "One Pot Beef & Pork Keema Aloo",
      "ingredients": ["beef", "pork", "aloo"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "1057kcal",
        "protein": "43g",
        "carbs": "119g",
        "fat": "44g"
      },
      "tags": ["Beef", "Pork", "Aloo", "One-Pot"],
      "image_front": "images/beef_pork_aloo_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/beef_pork_aloo_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "017",
      "title": "Honey Sesame Beef & Pork Stir Fry",
      "ingredients": ["beef", "pork"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "687kcal",
        "protein": "35g",
        "carbs": "76g",
        "fat": "25g"
      },
      "tags": ["Beef", "Pork"],
      "image_front": "images/beef_pork_stir_fry_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/beef_pork_stir_fry_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "018",
      "title": "Oven Baked Bacon White Wine & Mushroom Risotto",
      "ingredients": ["bacon", "wine", "mushroom"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "637kcal",
        "protein": "23g",
        "carbs": "83g",
        "fat": "19g"
      },
      "tags": ["Bacon", "Wine", "Mushroom"],
      "image_front": "images/bacon_wine_mushroom_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/bacon_wine_mushroom_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "019",
      "title": "Chicken in Creamy Peppercorn Sauce",
      "ingredients": ["chicken", "potato"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "563kcal",
        "protein": "41g",
        "carbs": "66g",
        "fat": "19g"
      },
      "tags": ["Chicken", "Potato"],
      "image_front": "images/chicken_potato_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/chicken_potato_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "020",
      "title": "Creamy Chickpea Korma",
      "ingredients": ["chickpea", "rice"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "788kcal",
        "protein": "20g",
        "carbs": "105g",
        "fat": "32g"
      },
      "tags": ["Chickpea", "Rice", "Curry"],
      "image_front": "images/chickpea_korma_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/chickpea_korma_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "021",
      "title": "Curried Lentil & Chicken Soup With Garlic Roti",
      "ingredients": ["chicken", "lentil", "roti"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "717kcal",
        "protein": "55g",
        "carbs": "99g",
        "fat": "11g"
      },
      "tags": ["Chicken", "Lentil", "Roti"],
      "image_front": "images/chicken_lentil_roti_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/chicken_lentil_roti_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "022",
      "title": "Crispy Sausage & Tomato Risotto With Baby Kale",
      "ingredients": ["sausage", "kale", "rice", "risotto"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "765kcal",
        "protein": "29g",
        "carbs": "91g",
        "fat": "33g"
      },
      "tags": ["Sausage", "Kale", "Rice", "Risotto"],
      "image_front": "images/sausage_kale_risotto_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/sausage_kale_risotto_back.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "023",
      "title": "Creamy Truffle Mushroom Naanizza",
      "ingredients": ["chips", "mushroom", "naan"],
      "nutrition": {
        "calories": "901kcal",
        "protein": "23g",
        "carbs": "116g",
        "fat": "38g"
      },
      "tags": ["Chips", "Mushroom", "Naan"],
      "image_front": "images/chips_mushroom_naan_front.webp",
      "image_back": "images/chips_mushroom_naan_back.webp"
    }
  ]
}